superearners.com 2014-05-23

# PRIVACY POLICY

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us and we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

We gather two types of information about users: 

\- Information that users provide through voluntary submissions ie name, address, email address, telephone number, etc.   
\- Information we gather through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. 

Under no circumstances do we divulge any information about an individual user to a third party. 

_User supplied_

Information provided voluntarily by our users, ie their personal details, email addresses, preferences, etc.

 _Usage tracking_

We track individual user stats throughout our site. This is to ensure that we continually improve our products. 

_Cookies_

As is standard safe practice with most websites on the internet (like banks, etc), we may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. 

**Sharing Of The Information**

Your email address and other personal details will never be hired, sold, lent or given to any third party. We will use your email address to communicate with you and to send you updates, enhancements, news and promotions relating to our service. We may be obliged to pass any userâ€™s details to any law enforcement agency or court of law if the user is being investigated for or suspected of any crime.

**Childen**

Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

It's very easy to get started right away. Place your order now and get immediate access to the Members Area! You will be given a username and password immediately. Log into the Members Area and begin typing and earning rightaway! 

**Super Earners Lifetime Membership**  
for only **~~$149~~ Special Offer: Today only $60.00** (once-off)  
**INSTANT ACTIVATION**  
**30 day Money Back Guarantee**  
  
---  

If you wish to pay by e-gold, click the logo below:
